<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Jules Sandoz - Blog</title><link>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Jules Sandoz - Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:46:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Transforming into a Manager</title><link>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/transition-collaborator-manager/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:46:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/transition-collaborator-manager/</guid><description>Becoming a manager is a big step in one&amp;rsquo;s career. It can be a challenging and rewarding experience, but it&amp;rsquo;s not always easy. The transition from being an individual contributor to leading a team can be difficult, and it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the unique challenges that come with the role. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore what can be learned to transition well into management and how to be a better manager.</description></item><item><title>Comparing Angular and Vue: A Media Engineering Student's Perspective</title><link>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/vue-vs-angular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:10:47 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/vue-vs-angular/</guid><description>As a media engineering student, I have had the opportunity to work with a variety of front-end JavaScript frameworks and libraries. Two of the most popular ones are Angular and Vue. Both Angular and Vue are powerful tools for building dynamic and interactive user interfaces, but they have some key differences that make them better suited for certain types of projects.
Angular is a complete framework that provides a lot of built-in features and tools for building large-scale, complex web applications.</description></item><item><title>Become a better developer: Tips and Tricks</title><link>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/become-a-better-developer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:03:48 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/become-a-better-developer/</guid><description>As a media engineering student, I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning a lot about web development and the different aspects that come with it. From coding best practices to time management, there are many things to consider when trying to improve as a developer. In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing some tips and tricks that I&amp;rsquo;ve found to be particularly useful in my own journey to becoming a better developer.
1. Master the basics Link to heading One of the most important things to keep in mind as a developer is to master the basics of the language you&amp;rsquo;re working with.</description></item><item><title>How to Become an Outsanding Manager in Development and Front-End Engineering</title><link>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/become-outstanding-manager-development-frontend-engineering/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:06:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://julessandoz.github.io/labveilletech/posts/become-outstanding-manager-development-frontend-engineering/</guid><description>Being a manager in development and front-end engineering can be a challenging task. However, by understanding the common pitfalls and best practices, you can become an outstanding leader for your team.
Acquiring Technical Skills Link to heading First, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to treat management as a technical skill that must be acquired. Many new managers overlook the need to study management in the same way they might learn a new framework or language.</description></item></channel></rss>